Downloaded from
HQCINEMAS.COM
Official HQCINEMAS movies site:
Thanks so much for
coming on the show today.
Well, my pleasure.
Thanks for having me.
And I can't believe
the success you've had.
Your book and still
riding number one?
Number one, New York Times.
Yeah, so I'm very lucky
and I'm very grateful.
And I know you can't say too
much about what's coming up,
but it's my understanding
you're working
on a book about mythology
in the Americas?
Yeah, you're right.
I can't really tell
you too much about it.
But what I can say is
that it does squarely
focus on the mythos and
mythology surrounding
fear and the concept of fear.
When can your fans
expect..
I'm still really deep into
the research into the book.
I to Northern
California to a very particular
area that permeates fear.
Fear, just as an emotion is
a manifestation of something
that we always perceive
as just kind of a concept.
It's not a concept.
Fear is very real.
Well, sounds like
The New York Times
better make room for
another bestseller.
I hope so.
Your lips to God's ears.
Diving this deeply into
fear, as you described it--
Yeah.
-does it strike fear in you?
No.
So we've
been covering this story
for quite a while, but it
seems like today's news might
be the final chapter in one of
the most bizarre stories we've
had, the story of Angel Wilson.
If you remember, Angel is
the missing 26-year-old
from 2015 who was
camping in the Tahoe area
and never returned home.
Investigators--
Babes, turn it off.
Hold on, listen.
Once they found
that two of the friends
that had accompanied her
were discovered deceased
from apparent suicide.
Turn it off.
And
today, news has broke
that her remains might have--
Said
that he's a Gemini.
Said that he liked the
one to see her in that.
Turned around and
changed his mind.
Thank you, babe, for
getting me out of the house.
We sure chose the best
time to get away, right?
Was I driving you crazy or
were you driving me crazy?
Why do you think I'm
taking you on this trip?
Thank you.
All right, but, listen, I just
don't want you all on top of me
when you see what
I'm taking you, OK?
Yeah, yeah, OK.
You're going to have
to behave yourself.
When's the last time
you saw me in a dress?
It's been a while.
Thank you for wearing it.
I'm surprised it still fits.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I needed to
get out of that office.
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
You ready for this?
What are you up to?
Would you stop trying
to figure everything out?
I told you, I want
this to be a surprise.
So you're just going to get
out on the side of the road?
Bianca, what are you doing?
You don't have to wear that.
Not up here.
You have to wear this.
I told you, I want
this to be a surprise.
The only way that's going to
work is by blindfolding you.
Please?
I cannot believe I'm going
to let you blindfold me.
I am the luckiest
man in the world.
Yeah you are, you've
got two minutes.
Two minutes.
All I need.
In my deep depress, I
am for a moment feels all up--
wanted.
Thought I was in control.
That's a trick back.
Thinking I had earned
love, going out bad.
God, I'm scared of
me, afraid to speak.
I've noticed.
Every time--
All right, stay put.
Cannot believe
I let you blindfold me.
It's
hard for me to see.
Too fast.
You've been good to us.
Mademoiselle.
You need your inhaler?
Thank you.
Just give me a second.
You OK?
Come on, get out here.
Breathe some of this
clean mountain air.
Oh, two seconds away
from taking this thing off.
No, no, no, we're almost done.
Five more steps.
You're crazy.
I miss--
Step.
Two steps.
Lift up your right foot.
Right.
OK, I'm taking them off.
No, not yet.
Trying to find the perfect spot.
Stay right there.
Afraid that you got
to choose, help me decide.
ROM: OK.
You ready?
Oh yeah, I'm ready.
My tears-- will flow.
Take it off.
Oh, Rom.
It's beautiful.
What is this?
We're here to
celebrate your birthday.
I just figured everything that's
going on in the world right now
and me finally getting the
book to the publishers--
Happy birthday Bianca!
Bianca!
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Go say hi.
Come on, go, go, go!
What?
-Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday, baby.
Who?
Who do I give--
Me, me, me.
Happy birthday.
Beautiful.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Happy birthday!
Woo!
All right, guys, look
what we have for you.
Come on in.
- What?
- Wow.
Check It out.
Check it out.
Wow.
Look at this.
Look at that, huh?
What up, dog!
Ah.
Yeah, yeah.
Lou.
Hey.
Yes.
I am so sorry I'm late.
He didn't do it.
What do you mean?
Did you give him the ring?
He had the ring.
I think he got nervous.
Nervous?
Does she know?
Lou!
Hey.
Do my eyes deceive me?
Forest Park's finest Lou Powell.
What up?
Ah, it means so much to me.
Thank you.
How could I not?
Hey, when was the last
time all of us were together?
Year ago, Detroit.
I don't know.
Was it that night
at Coney Island?
Coney Island, yeah,
back in the day.
Oh my god.
I miss y'all.
The D's big three, yeah.
Yo, man, Lou wants
to talk to you.
What's up, Lou?
What happened?
Thanks, Russ.
You wasn't going to tell him.
Bro, everybody came here.
It was perfect.
What happened?
I don't know.
I can't believe I did it again.
Again?
How many proposals
have you botched?
Three, four, four.
Four?
This is number four,
lucky number four.
Well, at least
you're consistent.
It wasn't the right time.
Right time?
You had the ring?
I had the ring.
She was there?
Yeah.
So what the fuck you mean
it wasn't the right time.
Lou, Lou, Lou,
chill, chill, chill.
Look, look, look,
we're here for you.
We got tested.
We came here to support you.
Whatever goes down out
here, we're your boys.
Grow a pair.
Get a ring.
Hit a knee.
Let's put a ring
on her finger.
Can we do that, gentlemen?
That's what I'm saying.
All right?
All right.
OK, look, the weekend
is not over with.
I'm going to find
the perfect time.
Guys--
OK?
Just trust me.
Guys, guys, guys.
Big three from
the D. Let's get it.
Let's go.
I'm going to make it
happen, three from the D.
Big three from the D.
All right, everyone,
gather round.
Gather round.
Got the whole
weekend to catch up.
Now that we're all here, I'd
like to be the first to say,
welcome to the historic
Strawberry Lodge.
We've got this all to ourselves
for the entire weekend.
Not exactly the Four Seasons.
More like one season, fall--
ing apart.
Oh, god, OK, come on, guys.
Thank you, Benny.
But we don't need that.
All right?
I would like you all to
meet the lovely Ms. Winrich.
Thank you.
Good evening, everyone.
And welcome to the
Strawberry Lodge.
I'm absolutely sure
that you'll all come
to love it as much as I do.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean any
disrespect by it.
Sometimes, I just mess
around with Michael to bring
his ego down a few notches.
The place is actually
really beautiful.
I took some pictures earlier.
Hm.
Ms. Winrich was kind enough
to open up this entire lodge
especially for us and was
also the maestro in helping
make this an A1 weekend.
So, basically, be
nice, assholes.
I'd like to ask you to
gather together for one photo.
It's an old tradition
we have here.
We like to memorialize
all who stay with us.
That way, you never leave.
I feel like I'm in
"Get Out" right now.
All right, guys,
let's go, let's go.
All right, all right.
Don't dirty up my white.
I feel good.
Let me get on of you.
There you go.
All right, then on three,
one, two, oh.
Oh!
Can we do one more for us?
OK, shout out to the
time machine she used
to go get that Polaroid camera.
Three--
OK.
All right.
Thank you.
You're going to the guest one.
Good to see you.
It's such a pleasure
to have you with us.
I want to welcome you
especially to Strawberry Lodge.
Thank you.
You carry the light, my dear.
I can see it.
You're a beacon.
Congratulations.
Ah--
Yes, yes, we're all very proud
that Rom finished his new book.
In fact, you know what?
Before we leave, I'll
get you a signed copy.
How's that?
That would be lovely.
And I have something
for you before I
leave you guys for the weekend.
Me?
Yes.
I'd like to give this to you.
It's our own bottle of wine.
This place just keeps
getting better and better.
This is something we
give all our guests.
Thank you very much.
I'll make sure we toast
with this tonight.
Wow.
You know what?
Being out in the
mountains is probably
what the doctor ordered.
No, what the
doctor's ordered is
for us to be social
distanced and sanitize
every time we blink.
Can you for once
stop being a nurse
and try to have a good time?
We're 106.
Here we go.
Look, right here.
Whatever's in this
old ass room, woosah.
We're going to
appreciate it, all right?
All right.
Oh.
OK.
This is cool.
It's cute.
It's not bad.
What is she looking at?
White people are into
some strange shit.
You like it?
Yeah.
It's rustic, isn't it?
You know, this place
was built in 1838.
Burned down, got rebuilt in '53.
This looks like the
original furniture.
It's so beautiful.
And all the history here,
Native American culture,
into the Spanish.
Gold rush happened right
here, just down all the way
from Sonora up to Tahoe.
Everything OK?
You didn't have to do this.
I did.
I did have to do this.
For you.
For us.
My birthday was
a week ago, Rom.
But these last couple
years have been crazy for us,
between you getting your
doctorate in religion
and me finally finding
a little bit of success.
Besides, this place, there's
so much history right here.
OK, there you go.
So you're already writing
your next book now?
No, no, I--
I know what it looks like.
But I promise you,
it's not that.
Hey.
I just wanted you to
have this trip to remind
you how special you are to me.
My
dear, you're a beacon.
Stop.
Your nose, it's bleeding.
You OK
Yeah, fine.
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm going to go hang out with
the girls for a little bit.
Cool?
Yeah, totally cool.
Bye-bye, Mrs. Winrich.
She got a--
No, no, no, no, I correct you.
As of two weeks
ago, Rom Jennings
is a bestselling author.
Did I not tell you
a year ago that we'd
be having this conversation?
What does it matter what
anyone says about this deal
if I'm his agent?
Hello?
Oh, you fucker.
Come on.
Give me a bar.
Give me a bar in this old bitch.
Woo!
Hey.
Hey, Mike.
I want you to forget
about what happened outside.
No, listen, do not give
yourself a hard time.
There's a lot of people.
That's a lot pressure.
Rom, it's going to
be a great weekend.
You're going to turn it around.
You're going to get
it done, all right?
It's going to work
out great, OK?
OK.
Listen, in other news,
the phone has been ringing.
And I know you've
been doing research.
I'm going to need an outline
from you sooner or later.
I don't want to talk
about that right now.
- Rom, forget it.
- Not right now.
I'm not even
talking about work.
Who's talking about work?
But-- I need fucking
outline, all right?
OK?
OK.
All right, listen, 30
minutes, I want everyone
changed over by the firepit.
I'll arrange something special.
It's going to be a vibe.
The girls are going
to love it, all right?
Thank you, Michael.
I got you.
We're good.
This place is
perfect for both of us.
Take this.
Go and have fun with
your friends, all right?
Thanks.
You know that
lady from earlier?
Mm-hm.
You think she's leaving soon?
Because she don't got
a sign on the desk.
She's already left, babe.
But, apparently, it's
actually a really cool story.
So her family bought
the lodge when it first
burnt down in the late 1800s.
They rebuilt what
was left of it.
They renamed it
Strawberry Lodge.
And now they rent it out
to people on the weekends.
Who told you all this?
Rom.
What?
Rom think he's so slick.
Why do you say that?
Rom brought us out here
to do research for his book.
This whole thing is like
the backdrop for another Rom
Jennings bestselling novel.
Oh!
Stay right there.
You OK?
Guys, firepit, please.
Everyone's waiting.
All right, for
anybody who's interested,
this quaint little mountain town
that we're in right now used
to be part of Mexico
until 1848 when
it was ceded to United States.
And then became Strawberry,
California in '49,
during the Gold Rush.
Now, the gold
brought belligerent,
but determined
miners and outlaws,
fueled by whiskey and greed.
Now, they came here for one
reason and one reason only--
gold!
Oh my-- stop!
Stop.
You can't.
Yo, I'mma go inside if y'all
keep going.
No, no, keep going.
Keep going, Rom.
Keep going.
And they got their
gold, all right.
So these miners began
to prey on the natives.
They went into their
villages and stole
their women during the night.
And these women decided
they had had enough.
And they made a pact.
They called themselves
las bruja and set it up
so they would control the town.
Documented reports
state that these women
were able to control
the miners minds
and make them hallucinate
to the point they
were so frightened
they would kill
themselves to escape the fear.
Bullshit.
Bro, why would
you tell us right
now when we've got to go sleep?
How am I going to sleep tonight?
Oh, that baby's scared.
I think we can all agree
that if we've learned anything,
it's that we've had to
face a lot of fears.
And I am so fucking
tired of being scared--
scared of going outside,
scared of taking
chances, scared of doing
the things we love.
So why don't we make a pact?
Let's all tell each other
our most personal fears
and just let them go.
Fear will not rule
us here, not tonight.
Let's do it.
I'll start.
When I was 18 years
old, I got hit by a car.
And in that moment,
I wasn't in control.
It was terrifying.
And the only thing that didn't
break was this necklace.
So my greatest fear
is losing control.
And as long as I
wear this necklace,
no matter what life
brings me, I know that I'm
going to be in control.
OK, who's next?
Birthday girl?
Where do I start?
Growing up in a
religious household,
I feared the consequences
of losing my faith.
It's why I read a Bible
verse every night,
pray without ceasing.
Being an asthmatic, air
is so precious to me.
And now that air could kill me.
My biggest fear
has become losing
the thing I took for granted
the most, just breathing.
Wow, OK.
I'll take-- I'll
take a shot at it.
You know, where we
come from in Detroit,
you know, there's not a lot
of options or opportunities.
I made a promise to
everyone that I would make
it out of there no matter what.
And my word is my
bond, always has been.
What we're from, it'll
kill you if it isn't.
So I have to say my biggest
fear is not being trusted,
especially by the people
who are depending on me.
So back in the
day, Lou convinces
me and Rom to go to the movies
and see "Boyz n the Hood."
At the end of the movie when
Morris Chestnut is running
and he gets sprayed in
the chest and blood starts
flying all over the place--
Oh, man, before me and
Lou had to carry you out,
you're staring at the
screen in a trance.
And you just go, "Ricky!"
"Ricky!"
So good.
What is your fear specifically?
My biggest fear is blood.
There's just something about
it that I can't handle.
So my biggest
fear, as a mother,
is honestly just not being
able to provide for my son.
My biggest fear is drowning.
I can't swim.
Except for baths.
This woman will take a
bath for three hours.
Oh, man.
Claustrophobia, 100%.
When I was a kid, my
older brother used to lock
me in the drawer under my bed.
Used to be locked
in there for hours
in the dark flailing around.
So, yeah, that's why I'm
getting cremated when I die.
Small, confined spaces,
coffins, not for me.
I was in high school.
I got pulled over.
Cop didn't give me a reason.
He just reached
inside my window,
snatched me out, slammed my
head on the hood of the car.
I was terrified.
So I say, fuck the cops
and fuck handcuffs.
That's easy for me.
My biggest fear is losing you.
Bullshit.
I'll tell you what, you
guys put this fire out.
Let's set things up inside.
I'm going to get
that bottle of wine
that the lovely Mrs.
Winrich gave us, yeah?
Woo!
To us.
Best weekend of our lives.
Cheers to a great
weekend and happy birthday.
-Hey, Michael.
-What's up, Michael?
Where you been?
We've been waiting on you.
Michael.
Just, uh, so I know
I keep saying this,
but you guys have no idea
what a great weekend we
have ahead of us.
Thanks for all being here.
So let's, let's kind of
close this evening off
with a nice toast to
the birthday girl--
Thank you.
-to new books, being with
people you love in crazy times.
Yeah?
Mm-hm.
All right, let's
get some glasses.
What did she drink tonight?
Whoa.
There we go.
That's the spirit
we need though.
That's the spirit we need.
Hey.
Cheers.
Yeah, salud.
Woo.
And to Bianca.
La familia.
Yes.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh my god.
Yo, what the fuck
is in here, man?
The fuck?
What the fuck is this shit?
This is why I
don't fucking drink.
Please, just put
your glasses down.
Maybe it's just old wine?
Let's just forget it happened.
Uh-uh.
If anybody wants
to drink any more,
there's a couple more
bottles of champagne
and a bottle of
tequila at the bar.
It's got like a-- it's got
like an aftertaste to it.
Let's go.
Sandpaper or something.
Guys!
No, but seriously,
what was that?
I have no idea.
What did it taste like?
Uh, man, go.
Throw that shit away, man.
I will.
It's disgusting, man.
1938?
God's word is sure.
When God begins to
speak,
will rise up and live.
And things that ought to be
dead will lay down and die.
When the word of the lord God
can speak a word to you and and
shall be healed!
Hey, I'm sorry about the wine.
How do we know everyone got
tested before we came up here?
Because everyone got tested.
What are you talking about?
I mean, how do we know?
Because I arranged the test.
That's how we know.
What's the problem?
Lou.
What about Lou?
Lou is sick.
Dude, Lou's not sick.
He got tested like
everyone else.
And how do you know he
physically went and got tested?
Bro, I'm telling you,
I've been watching him.
Ever since we got here,
he's been coughing.
And not just easy cough, like
he's been coughing up a lung.
I'm telling you, he's sick--
Benny, Benny, relax, relax.
On my way to bed,
I will go and check
on Lou, make sure he's OK.
I need you to concentrate on
having a good time, all right?
Relax.
And if
god is panicking, oh my god.
You may as well slit your
wrists and your throat.
What are you doing?
Mrs. Winrich low
key got some classics.
Let me find out.
Oh, oh, baby girl.
You ain't getting
none to that music.
We'll see about that.
Good night.
Sorry about the wine.
No worries.
Hey, Lou, what a night, huh?
What up, doe?
Listen, I want to
ask you a question.
Don't take it personally.
I feel very stupid even asking.
Nah, no stupid
questions, go ahead.
Shoot.
OK, OK, how are you feeling?
You feeling all right?
What?
How am I feeling?
I feel fine.
Yeah, you know, not
me, you know, a couple
of-- a couple of the others--
A couple of the others?
Yeah, a couple of the
other guys mentioned they
saw you coughing--
So you came up here--
Absolutely not.
-to accuse--
-me of being contagious--
No--
-of a disease and
being willing to spread
it to my closest friends.
That's what you're saying?
No, I'm just trying
to keep everything safe.
What gives you the right
to come up here and check me?
Just crossing the--
crossing the T, dotting
the I's, making sure--
Nah, man, I'm going to
dot your I. How about that?
How about I dot your I.
Mm--
Man, get out from
in front of my door.
I feel fine.
There's no need to get--
I took a test just like all
of you other motherfuckers
took a test.
Fuck out my face.
Squirrely mouth
looking motherfucker.
It's been good that
we've been getting
closer over the last few years.
You're still here?
I'm going.
Goodnight.
If you need anything.
Please come home.
Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh, baby girl.
Murder-suicide, suicide,
suicide.
Murder-suicide.
Suicide, suicide.
The body of a woman inside.
It's playing backwards.
Murder-suicide.
Suicide, suicide.
The
body of a woman inside.
Double murder-suicide.
Why would
she give us that?
I'm going to say something
when she gets back.
I mean, that was the weirdest
thing I've ever seen.
Mm-hm.
I mean, it just totally
ruined everything.
Totally.
It seems like
such a sick joke.
What do we do when we are
overwhelmed by evil thoughts?
Where do they come from?
And, more importantly,
how do they influence
our emotions and our actions?
In my
research, people
have described the most
violence and horrific thoughts
that they had.
But what is more frightening is
the sources of these ideations.
Angel of death?
"Wine used as
initiation ritual."
Angel Wilson.
That's great.
Turn around.
Aw, Angel.
What?
Wow.
This has got to be the place.
Found it.
What is this?
"By feeding these souls
of light to the portal,
the gatekeeper will
be granted immortality
to fulfill their infinite
bondage to darkness?"
"Believing what you fear
will bring to the victim
what they are afraid of."
"Once the ritual of la
uva, the grape, is completed,
the collecting of
souls may begin."
You OK?
Yeah.
You left the kettle on.
I was making tea.
OK.
Hey, you guys got
to see this right now.
Public health officials
announced that a mysterious
airborne contagion has
been identified as
the next major health
crisis in global society.
Its origin is unknown and
is spreading at a rate
like we've never seen.
Minutes ago, Washington
has confirmed
that multiple infections
of this deadly disease
have been confirmed in both
the East and West Coast.
The CDC warns
Americans take it serious.
The director of the CDC
has warned all Americans
to prepare for the worst.
Whatever you do,
do not go outside.
Secure all windows and doors.
Fear it.
The air is contaminated Droplets
can spread within seconds.
This airborne virus can
cause death within hours.
Fuck.
Make sure
that you are cautious--
We're basically trapped
in this lodge indefinitely.
After all these months and
now we can't even go outside?
We can't go outside.
The people you are in
contact with are infected.
It might only be
a couple of days.
How do you know that?
I don't.
I'm just hopeful.
Well, let's get real.
Let's talk about it.
Talk about what?
Who is missing?
What do you mean, Benny?
Why don't you look around
and tell me who's missing?
Oh.
Mike, say something.
Russ, say something.
You guys talk to him.
Lou is sick.
I mean, why are
you doing this?
Doing what?
He told you that
he has allergies.
He is infected, Rom.
Whatever the new
variant is, he has it.
Yeah, he looked,
he looked sick.
Hey, Russ, are you
buying into this bullshit?
I don't know, man.
He told us that
he's got allergies.
Why would he lie to us?
He's our family.
That's why we're here.
No, we're here because you
two brought us in the middle
of fucking nowhere.
No, we were trying to do
something nice for someone.
It was someone's birthday.
No hospital.
Don't turn it around to
something that it wasn't.
Symptoms include
hallucination,
coughing, and dry mouth.
You're
all going to die.
This is probably the safest
place that we could be.
It's the safest place?
No hospital, no pharmacy,
no internet reception?
No fucking people.
No disease.
No virus.
I'm not dying because of
your lack of leadership.
What you wanna do?
It's OK.
You were sick.
Hey, knock it off.
We did not come this
far to watch us fucking
have a mental breakdown.
We need to take a deep breath
and figure out our options.
You saw Lou.
How did he look?
When I saw Lou last
night, he did not look good.
When you talked to
Lou, was he sick or not?
I'm not a doctor, but I
would say that Lou is sick.
I'm sorry to say,
his symptoms are
in line with the new strain.
Guys, the only
sensible thing to do
is to get Lou out of this house.
I agree.
Excuse me.
You heard what the CDC said.
There's some crazy
stuff going on outside.
Yeah, I heard what they said.
He's staying here.
And you're going to
decide that for everyone?
You're damn right.
How is that fair?
Maybe you're sick.
How about that, Michael?
Maybe you have to go.
I don't feel sick.
Hey, guys.
Kimmy, what are you doing?
I'm-- I'm leaving.
You can't go now.
Listen, I have
space in the back
if anyone wants to
come and join me.
Fuck.
Have you seen the news?
No mask is going to
protect you from that.
The air is contaminated.
People are dying outside, Kimmy.
My son is at home
with this babysitter.
I can't even get through to her.
I have to be at
home with my son.
They said you
can't go outside.
It's not--
Benny, Benny, people, if
she wants to go, let her go.
She's got a kid at home.
My gosh, she's got
kid at home you
cannot go out there like that.
What choice do I have?
It's not safe.
You don't know what
you're up against.
Just--
That's my son.
And you would do the
exact same thing.
It doesn't make
any fucking sense.
I love you.
I love you all.
Just be safe.
You're just going
to let her go?
Baby, she has a kid, baby.
Come on.
No, we-- we can't
just let her go.
We have to let her go,
B. It's poison out there.
You can't risk it.
All of this is crazy, bro.
How do we know that
we're not infected?
Because we're not sick, Russ.
Because we're fine.
We're fine.
How do you know
that we're fine?
The CDC said the symptoms of
paranoia and hallucination.
I know I am not
the only one that's
seeing things in this lodge.
I've been seeing things too.
What?
What did you see?
It's not important.
Maybe you just
need a little rest.
I saw some shit.
Sorry.
I'm fine.
It's asthma.
Serena, you know it's asthma.
Serena?
I just-- my inhaler.
Serena, you know it's Bianca.
She's got asthma.
Can you help her out?
All right, yeah, yeah.
This is what we need to do.
You guys get her upstairs, let
her get a little bit of rest.
Guys, we're in this together.
Guys, do not let
this break us apart.
Let's not lose control.
All right, all
right, all right.
You're going to lie back here.
Go on.
Deep breath.
Hope Kimmy makes it.
Bianca, do you
think you're sick?
No.
OK.
Wait, get my bag for me.
Yeah.
You're pregnant.
When did you find out?
Three weeks ago, maybe.
You know, I--
I just knew.
Does Rom know?
No.
OK.
I-- I mean, there's
so much going on.
I haven't found the
right time, I guess.
I don't know.
And then he's just not
here, it feels like.
Hey Lou, how are you doing?
Everybody lost their
minds over this virus.
Think I'm infected, huh?
I'm not dumb.
And Michael coming
up here trying,
trying to figure me out.
He's paranoid.
We're paranoid.
And everybody thinks they're
a doctor all of a sudden.
I think maybe we all have it.
Hey, listen, man, I
told you, on my life,
I quarantined two
weeks before this trip.
It's my allergies, you know?
I already gave y'all
the God's honest truth.
I know you did, Lou.
I would never doubt you.
Looking for a
tarp, tape, anything
we can block windows up with.
Fuck off.
Yo, it's kind of
creepy down here.
Benny, Benny, come on, huh?
Yo, Mike.
What?
Come here.
Looks like something back here.
Hold on, watch out.
We're going to figure
a way out of this.
Yeah, we always do.
Since eighth grade, right?
Yeah.
Listen, well, when
I look in your eyes
and I see the look
in her eyes, I could
tell you found the one, bro.
Don't fuck this up.
You know we came
here for a show, man.
So before this weekend's over,
there better be fireworks.
You understand me?
I'm going to get it done, Lou.
Don't be afraid of commitment.
You don't
want to be like me,
coming home to an empty house
every night, no kids, no woman,
no one to take care of you.
Fear is a choice.
Don't believe in it.
All right?
Now, be out.
I'll be much better
after I get some rest.
Go tell them that.
Yo, Mike, come here?
What you got there?
I don't know.
About to find out.
It's got to be
stuff behind it.
I'm so glad you guys are here.
Me too.
What?
It's probably an
allergic reaction, right?
Not a symptom.
OK, enough about me.
You want me to get you
something for your stomach?
Some tea?
Yeah.
Why is there a bed down here?
It's fucking weird.
It's an old lodge, isn't it?
Lots of shit down here.
There's no windows
here, is there?
No.
So no ventilation to
the rest of the house.
Did you get a hold of Kim yet?
No, I've called.
I've texted.
It just goes to voicemail.
Maybe she doesn't
have reception.
I don't know.
Bianca.
What?
Oh.
My necklace, I must
have dropped it in here.
I just had it.
Have you seen it?
No, no, I don't
think you had it on.
No, I wear my necklace
all the time, Bianca.
Calm down immediately.
No, I literally just had it.
Why are you looking
at me like I'm sick?
It's a rash from an
allergic reaction.
Just calm down.
Just had my necklace
and now it's gone.
Hey, hold this for a second.
Are those empty bottles
of that shitty wine we had?
Yeah, Russ.
Fuck.
What you got down there, Benny?
Looks like some old
chest,..
I don't see
anything good, man.
Russ, Hold up a second.
"Believing what you fear
will bring to the victim
what they are afraid of."
This is it.
Upstairs
room isn't sealed.
Obviously, not waterproof.
Lou, I know he's your
friend, but he is sick.
There's a room down here.
We can easily put him in there.
There's no ventilation
to the rest of the house.
We can get food and
water down to him.
I don't want to get sick.
What is this?
Benny, can I talk
to you real quick?
Hey.
Rom.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm listening.
Are you?
Yeah, I promise.
Something's wrong.
Listen.
I don't know what it is.
Babe, listen to me.
Last night when
I couldn't sleep,
I ended up running
around the house.
And I ended up in
the basement when
I found these photos and books.
And-- you got to listen to this.
"Seeking those of
light and sourcing
fears from each soul for
fear and faith are the same."
We are trapped.
You hear me?
We're in this weird ass
lodge in this weird ass
town in the middle of nowhere.
We can't go outside.
You guys saw the news.
We have no idea what this mist
will do if we walk into it.
And I'm not trying to
die being a character
in one of Rom's books.
The way we're going to go
down is from the inside out.
And the only person that's
showing symptoms right now
is Lou.
So here's what
we're going to do.
We're going to put Lou
down here in this basement.
Do you hear yourself?
I know.
Lou is my best friend.
I love Lou more
than anybody here.
We need to bring Lou
to this basement.
And we need to lock that
motherfucking door until we
can figure this shit out.
Listen to yourself.
We're going to put him
down here in a basement?
It will only be for one night.
Lou would do the exact
same to us if he had to.
We've got to look
out for the girls
and we've got to look
out for the group.
You mean you got to do
what's best for yourself?
Mike, you with me?
Benny you in?
Benny, look at me.
Are you in?
And what if he
don't want to come?
If it's between him
and us, we're going
to make him come down here.
Let's go.
Come on, Benny.
Look at this place.
Look at these women.
This is the lodge where they
were tortured and killed.
I don't know
what is up with you
in this freaky, crazy
obsession that you have.
But you need to listen to me.
I'm listening.
No, you're not.
I've been trying--
I've been trying to
tell you something
for the last two weeks.
Tell me?
What could you possibly
tell me that I haven't
heard in the past two weeks?
I'm pregnant.
Breathe.
It's going to be OK.
I want to go home.
Lou, Lou.
What's up?
Lou, come with us.
Come with us downstairs.
What you talking about,
come to you downstairs?
Rom needs our help, man.
What do you
mean, he need help.
Rom needs-- Rom needs help.
Rom got hurt, Rom.
Rom from hurt?
For what?
What you have?
How?
He was moving stuff
around in the basement.
He hurt himself.
He needs our help
downstairs now.
Rom needs our help, man.
Oh, can't really be sick.
Right in.
Follow me.
It's all right, just follow me.
I got you .
Bro, I got you.
He needs you.
How did he get down here?
He's here.
He needs you.
Just come on, man.
Where you at, bro?
This way.
Rom!
Where he at?
Go.
What are you doing?
What y'all doing?
You're sick.
Ah!
Fuck off me, man.
This is what
we're doing, Russ?
Open the door.
Open this door, Russ!
I'll be infected.
His own blood infected me, man.
I don't wanna fucking die.
Yo!
Just making--
Just get you upstairs.
Hold on.
Russ, it's OK.
I'm scared.
I don't wanna die.
Let's get you upstairs.
Please.
Goddamn, man.
I don't wanna fucking
die like this, man.
I know you ain't going
to leave me in here.
All right, sit down.
Ready?
We need to stop the bleeding.
And we need to clean him up.
I'll get something
to clean it maybe
and something to
put on the wound.
This side, this side.
Put the towel.
Russ, put pressure on it!
Aw, shit, man.
What the hell is happening?
Get out.
No, no, no, no.
Get out!
Babe.
What happened?
Babe, I'm sorry.
Keep pressure on it.
We just tried to put--
OK, here.
-Lou into the basement
real quick so that
he wouldn't get us all sick.
Basement?
We just didn't want him
to get everybody sick.
You understand that, right?
It just went down.
This is going to hurt.
Ah.
What were you thinking?
Keep it covered.
No, you can't touch me.
Baby, I'm not going anywhere.
Baby, hold on, back
away from me right now.
Open this!
Open this door!
I'm not leaving you.
Babe, getting you sick
would be worse than dying.
OK?
Baby, please.
I can't go.
Go lay down in
that bed right there.
I don't wanna.
Tomorrow morning, as long
as I don't have no symptoms,
we'll get in the car,
one way or the other,
and we're going to get
the fuck out of here.
You hear me?
Do you trust me?
I love you.
Now go.
Meg!
Wait.
What happened?
I'm sorry, man.
We just-- I don't know
what happened to me, bro.
Fuck.
You know I love Lou, right?
I'm sorry.
You know I would
never try to hurt him.
We just-- we just didn't want
him to get everybody sick.
Between this lodge
and the virus, man.
I'm going fucking crazy.
Bro, you don't understand, man.
Something got into me.
You believe me, right?
You know I would never
do that to him, right?
I know.
I'm going to go downstairs.
And I'm going to get Lou.
And I'll be back.
Tell Lou I'm sorry, man.
I'll be back.
Get Lou out of there, man.
Russ does not look good.
We've got to
get him some help.
There's got to be a
landline here somewhere.
I'm going to go
down to the front.
I'm going to get a
hold of the cops.
We can't stay here like this.
Get Lou out of that basement.
OK.
How is Russ?
What the fuck
were you thinking?
What was I thinking?
I'm thinking, shit, Lou is sick.
We should put him where he
can't get other people sick.
That's what I'm thinking.
No, Michael, you were only
thinking about yourself.
Now show me where you put him.
Now!
What the fuck?
What?
Somebody in here?
They don't trust you.
Sick.
You may as well come out now.
You're sick.
What's that?
What the--
They said you're sick.
They say you're sick.
They don't trust you.
They don't believe you.
Ugh.
Ah!
Ugh!
No!
We are experiencing
technical difficulties
at this time.
Please leave a message and
we will return your call--
What the fuck
were you thinking?
He's going to be pissed off.
Just make sure he
doesn't fucking hit me.
Why would he do that?
What the hell is this?
What language is that?
Oh, my god!
What is this?
No one's been here
for eight years?
She's scared.
We should have
been done already.
We all did it.
Got to do it.
Do it.
Sh.
Ah!
She looks like she's dying.
You look like you're dying.
Ah!
Why would he fucking do that?
Why would he fucking do that!
Hey, Michael?
What did he fucking do that?
It wasn't him.
Why would he fucking do that?
It wasn't him!
Michael, we--
This is my fucking fault.
We've all lost
something, Mike.
Rom?
Ah!
No, no, it's OK.
It's me.
You're OK.
We got to go.
We've got to get
out of here, OK?
Come on.
We're going to get your
medicine and get out of here.
Let's go.
We have to go.
We got to go.
I'm going to get the others.
Ah!
Mike!
A warning sign.
Russ?
Yet I wonder--
Mike, can you see her?
Oh, god.
She's there.
Oh, god!
Ah!
Oy, oy, no, no,
no, no, ah, ah, ah.
Ah!
Help!
Get me out of here!
Ah!
No, no.
Let me out!
What is going on?
Babe?
Serena?
Shut up!
Show me your hands.
I want to see your
hands right now.
You're OK.
Small breaths, come on.
Sit down.
It's not the virus.
It's the lodge.
Las brujas del miedo.
What?
It means the
witches of fear.
And they're using
our fear to kill us.
We got to get out of here now.
I can't go out there.
I'm so scared.
We have to leave now.
Yeah, you're OK.
No, no, no, no, I've been
seeing things out there.
I don't want to go out there.
I don't want to do it.
OK.
Everyone's dead.
What?
Everyone-- Michael,
Meg, Russ, all dead.
Everyone is dead.
There's something--
there's something
going on in this lodge.
I see the pictures of us, right?
All, all the pictures are
blurred except for who's
in this room right now.
I see Meg's picture.
Her face is blurred.
I go find Meg.
She's dead, OK?
I'm seeing the words.
I see, "no light Tamara."
At the bottom of the
painting, the numbers 4-1-9.
What does that mean?
Nolite, nolite, timere.
Nolite timere, it's Latin.
Nolite timere.
It means, don't be afraid.
OK, yes, OK, so, so,
what is it for 4-1-9?
Is the 4-1-9 code
for do not be afraid?
What does the 4-1-9 mean?
It's a scripture.
What is-- a scripture of what?
Scripture?
4-1-9, 4-1-9, 4-1-9,
4-1-9, I've seen that.
I've seen that number too.
Last night, when I told you
that story about the witches
and the miners and the lodge--
The witches?
-where they were
brought to be tortured.
That's here.
This is the lodge.
What the fuck are
you talking about, Rom?
There are places
all over the world
that are portals for evil.
What are you talking about?
What does that have
anything to do with what's
happening right now?
I'm trying to tell you.
Each one of these
portals has what
is called a
gatekeeper whose only
purpose is to feed the
portal souls, souls like us.
And they consume our souls to
give themselves eternal life
and to keep the portal alive.
The witches I told
you about last night?
They live in these portals.
Las brujas del miedo.
What?
It means the witches of fear.
You've lost your fucking mind.
The woman that was downstairs
that checked us in,
she's like a gatekeeper?
Yes.
Did you know this before
you brought us here?
I thought it was
just a story, Serena.
You thought it was just--
I didn't know.
I was just trying
to research my book.
Why would you bring us here?
I didn't know.
But what I do know is that
they are feeding on our fear.
And everything
that we are seeing,
everything that we are feeling,
I don't believe it's real.
So everything we're
seeing isn't real?
It is if you believe it.
And if you believe
it, it will kill you.
Babe, what are you doing?
We have to get out of here now.
Just give me a minute, OK?
Give me a second.
This is on you.
Our friends are dead
because of you, Rom.
I'm sorry.
Isaiah chapter 41 verse 9.
I have taken you to
the ends of the Earth.
From the farthest
corners, I called you
and not rejected you.
So fear not, for I am with you.
But I have chosen me
and not cast thee away.
You guys--
We've got to get out of here.
Come on.
Ah!
I think it's over.
Benny, it's OK.
It's not real.
What's that?
It's real.
It's not real.
We're manifesting fear.
We have to take a
chance and go outside.
The disease
is way more severe than anyone
could have actually imagined.
Oh my god.
Let's go.
I cried out.
And no one heard me.
And I was trying to get help.
It's OK.
You're OK.
We've got to go.
We got to take
our chances outside.
Come on.
We just got to run.
Sh.
Put this on.
Don't breathe until
we get to the car.
Ah!
We have to go get her.
Hell no.
You're crazy.
Don't go down there.
What y'all doing?
Stop!
Serena?
Serena.
What's up, man?
Step out of the car.
You know I ain't do nothing.
You ain't got to shine
the light in my face.
I didn't do nothing.
I said, get
out of the car now.
What ya'll doing, man?
I said I ain't doing nothing.
I'm just driving home.
Man, I ain't do nothing.
Serena.
Oh, god.
Ah!
Serena?
No, no.
Serena, what's happening?
We've got to go!
Serena, Serena, Serena,
whatever you're seeing,
it's inside your head.
Help!
It's not real.
Serena!
Don't believe it.
Help!
Serena, we're here.
Come to us.
We're here.
Ah!
Benny!
What-- what?
Oh, my god.
Benny.
Baby, keep going.
We've got to go.
I told you I
didn't do nothing!
I'm sorry.
I'm s--
We need to get out.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Benny, what did you do?
I had to.
Don't do it, Benny.
Benny, no!
Ah!
I can't feel my legs.
We have to go.
Bianca, I'm sorry.
You know you can't
beat it physically.
You have to beat it mentally.
You can beat this thing.
Don't lose your faith.
I love you.
Now go.
Ah!
Bianca, it's not real.
Oh!
Ah!
Come on, you can do it.
Use your faith.
It's taken you to
the ends of the Earth
from the farthest corners
and I've called you.
I will strengthen
you and help you.
I called you and
not rejected you.
So fear not, for I am with you.
Do not be dismayed.
For I am your god!
And hold,
my richest hand.
Praying with you.
Do not be deceived,
for am I you god.
For I am with you.
Oh, that shit is on.
Let me drop some
shit like this here.
At night, I can't sleep.
I toss and turn.
Candlesticks in the dark,
visions of bodies being burned.
Four walls just
staring at a nigga.
I'm paranoid sleeping with
my finger on the trigger.
On the scene there,
another terrible story
today as WRLA's Brian Mann
brings us the
latest on who died.
Polive have spent hours--
Police have spent hours
of Sunday investigating--
Let me out!
Fear.
Fear exists in the mind.
Everybody afraid of something.
Everybody got religions
of their own kind.
Everybody prayed for something.
And I got to hold it down
for me and mine out here.
I can't play with nothing
but stay with your scary ass
in the house.
Think better thoughts.
If you need to save your
buddies, just whip it, man.
Somebody pinch me.
I had a dream.
Everything played out.
And my real life was
something I seen.
Something I seen.
I'm just trying to get
all that out my thoughts,
but it won't leave.
Somebody scream.
I'm the only one right
now that's in this house,
but I hear screams.
This is real life.
No, this ain't for thing for TV.
It can't be televised.
Every day a gamble.
You get up and roll the dice.
You never know what's waiting
for you on the other side,
on the other side.
I can see it in their eyes that
I'm something that they fear.
Homie caught his first body,
but he did it out of fear.
Survival of the fittest
don't mistake quietness.
Fear.
Claim you ready for
the smoke with no,
all I see is-- fear, fear.
You know I'm traumatized.
When I hear the front door,
you can see it in my eyes.
You ever felt like that close.
The only thing I know, is
you shouldn't trust the soul.
Probably the saints say.
When I still living with my
mama, I left the crib at 17.
If I don't say my prayer at
night, I have a bad dream.
Penitentiary chances, hope
I don't go to the bing.
Riding around in the traffic
with a thumper when I sling.
I'm hoping somebody hear me
so it don't fall on deaf ears.
I'm out here with the snakes
and the snake my biggest fear.
I ain't trying to speak
it into existence.
Hope I make myself clear.
But please provide me with
some assistance sometime.
I think death is near.
This is real life.
No, this ain't for TV.
It can't be televised.
Every day a gamble.
You get up and roll the dice.
You never know it's waiting
for you on the other side.
On the other side.
This is real life.
No, this ain't for TV.
It can't be televised.
Every day a gamble.
You get up and roll the dice.
You never know what's waiting
for you on the other side,
on the other side.
Zip code, no shoes,
marble floors.
Bitch tip toe.
Floatsies with your
bitch at the Crypto.
Yeah.
Bunny rabbit did grow.
Who's that peeping in my window?
Got me--
Tip toe, sing.
Let you slide.
Finna wrap them up in plastic,
just another homicide.
And I drop them off
like axes, but you
ain't no friend of mine.
And I can't trust them, nothing.
This is real life.
No, this ain't for TV.
It can't be televised.
Every day a gamble.
You get up and roll the dice.
You never know what's waiting
for you on the other side.
On the other side.
I can see it in their eyes that
I'm something that they fear.
Homie caught his first body,
but he did it out fear.
Survival of the fittest,
don't mistake quietness.
Fear.
Claim you ready for this
smoke, but no, but all I see
is fear, fear.
One-- take a minute
to kick it with me.
Let's talk about what
you're afraid of.
You're aware that
fear is something
that only exist in your mind.
So what you made of?
They're afraid of my growth.
Majority shit you
see is made up.
I put all my faith in
my god and make sure
we talk every time I wake up.
Like, listen, Lord,
I ain't no angel,
but, nigga, with feelings, Lord.
A good nigga with a good heart.
Did everybody trying
to turn it to the Lord.
And I know that me having faith
is the first step I gotta take.
The mean hitter, Lord.
So forgive me, Lord as I
put on these black gloves
and kill these niggas, Lord.
Fear.